Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Iconographic Collection, 1848-2005 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Thomas Veres Photographs and Negatives, 1963-1996 and undated, (60 boxes)
  - Photographs,1963-1996 and undated
    - 1-20-76. John Gray informal (Box TV12)
    - 1-21-76. John Rissmeeyer informal (Box TV12)
    - 1-26-76. Bernie Owette T.V. interview (Box TV12)
    - 1-27-76. Art Kramer studio portrait (Box TV12)
    - 1-28,29-76. Deltacos meeting, Deltacos party (Box TV12)
    - 1-30-76. Terry Boyle informal (Box TV12)
    - 1-31-76. The Machine (Box TV12)
    - 1-32-76. Carlton Humphries, Harley Black TV program (Box TV12)
    - 1-33-76. Production Christmas party (Box TV12)
    - 1-34-76. B. Owette--Stan Tarner music (Box TV12)
    - 1-35-76. Dennis Crosley studio portrait (Box TV12)
    - 1-36-76. John Loden studio portrait (Box TV12)
    - 1-37-76. LU FILIP (Box TV12)
    - 1-38-76. New arrival group (Box TV12)
    - 1-40-76. Glenn Fortenberry with students (Box TV12)
    - 1-41-76. Don Ayers (Box TV12)
    - 1-42-76. John Dunmar (Box TV12)
    - 1-43-76. Retarded Children's Christmas Tree (Box TV12)
    - 1-46-76. Health Boston Broadcasting Deltacos (Box TV12)
    - 1-47-76. Steve Bowen (Box TV12)
    - 1-49-76. Howard Abrams (Box TV12)
    - 1-50-76. Bella Monalo studio portrait (Box TV12)
    - 1-51-76. Ad of the Month group (Samsonite) (Box TV12)
    - 1-52-76. Hugh O'Connell (No negatives available) (Box TV12)
    - 1-53-76. Alun Jones (Box TV12)
    - 1-54-76. John Sharman (Box TV12)
    - 1-55-76. Rena Bartos informal (Box TV12)
    - 1-56-76. Ad of the Month II: Samsonite (Box TV12)
    - 1-57-76. Chuck Webb and Bonnie Cutler (Box TV12)
    - 1-58-76. Warren Aldoretta studio portrait (Box TV12)
    - 1-59-76. Sonnya Yuspeh and N. Dahalla (Box TV12)
    - 1-60-76. Evelyn Peirce retirement party (Box TV12)
    - 1-61-76. New arrival group (Box TV12)
    - 1-62-76. Bert Manning meeting (Box TV12)
    - 1-63-76. Bert Manning judging group (Box TV12)
    - 1-64-76. Rena Bartos Advertising Women's lunch (Box TV12)
    - 1-65-76. Jackie Treacy (Box TV12)
    - 1-66-76. Don Johnston Ad Age (Box TV12)
    - 1-67-76. Don Johnston and students (Box TV12)
    - 1-70-76. Dick Eyman studio portrait (Box TV12)
    - 1-71-76. STP group story (Box TV12)
    - 1-72,73-76. Citysin School group; group with Ted Wilson (Box TV12)
    - 1-74-76. New arrival group (Box TV12)
    - 1-75-76. Presentation with Clayton group (Box TV12)
    - 2-1-76. Frank Manaro (Box TV12)
    - 2-2,3,4-76. Ron Sherman Family (Box TV12)
    - 2-6-76. Ludwig Dochterman studio portrait (Box TV12)
    - 2-7-76. David Fryss (Box TV12)
    - 2-9-76. Ed Walsh (St. Patricks Day) (Box TV12)
    - 2-10-76. Ad Ager Tyler--T. Wilson (Box TV12)
    - 2-11-76. Jeremy Scorse and Jeanne Maraz (Box TV12)
    - 2-12-76. Dorothy Philips studio portrait (Box TV12)
    - 2-13-76. Bill Brown studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 2-14-76. Don Davis studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 2-16-76. Bob Clark studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 2-15,18-76. Jackie Tracy studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 2-17-76. Security Analyst Meeting (Box TV13)
    - 2-19-76. Clynton Dixon (Box TV13)
    - 2-20-76. New arrival group (Box TV13)
    - 2-21-76. Ann Wright and student group (Box TV13)
    - 2-22-76. T. Wilson Scholarship Present (Box TV13)
    - 2-23-76. Harold Blum, Kent State students (Box TV13)
    - 2-26-76. Lunch T. Wilson group, Walter Stanton (Box TV13)
    - 2-25,29-76. S.T.P. group (Box TV13)
    - 2-30-76. Jack Conroy studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 2-31,32,33,34-76. Wedgewood art group, account group, media group, still life (Box TV13)
    - 2-35,36,37-76. Jack Ball, Delta Willis (Box TV13)
    - 2-39-76. Annual Meeting (Box TV13)
    - 2-46,47,48-76. Bernise Owette, Bob Titsworth, Bob Roeke (Box TV13)
    - 2-49-76. New arrival group (Box TV13)
    - 2-50-76. Guard--Susanne (Box TV13)
    - 2-51-76. T. Wilson --Account group (Box TV13)
    - 2-52-76. Don Johnston: John Treasure English Award (Box TV13)
    - 2-54-76. Medical Poster winners lunch (Box TV13)
    - 2-53,56-76. Information Center story (Box TV13)
    - 2-57 to 66-76. Yustin Wallrapp; Rhoda Green; Rhoda Green and Norman O'Dell; Dennis Licuy; Susan Chamberlain, Bernice Mosesson; Margaret Spader; others (Box TV13)
    - 2-67-76. Dynamints Display (Box TV13)
    - 2-68-76. Amelia Grinstead studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 2-69-76. Frank Tomeo studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 2-70-76. Ellen Currie studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 2-71-76. New arrival group (Box TV13)
    - 2-72-76. Telecine G. Secunda (Box TV13)
    - 2-73-76. Allegheny group (Box TV13)
    - 2-74-76. T.V. Academy guests (Box TV13)
    - 3-1-76. Cormac Ryan (Box TV13)
    - 3-2-76. Gabriel Samuels (Box TV13)
    - 3-3-76. Amelia Grinstead informal (Box TV13)
    - 3-4-76. Frank Tomeo informal (Box TV13)
    - 3-5-76. Blood center (Box TV13)
    - 3-6-76. Art exhibition (Mrs. Frederico) (Box TV13)
    - 3-7-76. Effie Awards (Box TV13)
    - 3-9-76. CLIO (Box TV13)
    - 3-10-76. John Barnhill studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 3-12-76. Gabrielle Hermann studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 3-13-76. James Corrieri studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 3-14-76. Nharrman Dhalla studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 3-15-76. David Fries studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 3-16-76. Howard Holder studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 3-17-76. Fish Bowl Jewelry (Box TV13)
    - 3-18-76. Baseball game (Box TV13)
    - 3-19-76. Tiffany--Gene Secunda (Box TV13)
    - 3-20-76. New arrival group (Box TV13)
    - 3-22-76. New V.P. group with Bert Mannings (Box TV13)
    - 3-23,24,25-76. Marty Rose; Gaby Hermann; Howard Holder (Box TV13)
    - 3-26-76. Congoleum Award (Box TV13)
    - 3-27-76. Permanent International. Jewelry Exhibit (Box TV13)
    - 3-29-76. Wynn Walshe studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 3-30-76. Arthur King-studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 3-31-76. Catherine Ames studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 3-32-76. Monty Green and John Mahr party (Box TV13)
    - 3-33-76. New Account, Taylor (Box TV13)
    - 3-34-76. Charles Appling studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 3-35-76. Telephone Room story (Box TV13)
    - 3-36-76. Terry Laughren studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 3-37-76. New telephone number: Don Johnston and Ron Sherman (Box TV13)
    - 3-38,39-76. Robert King studio portrait informal (Box TV13)
    - 3-40,41,42-76. Eric Overcamp, Terry Monger (Box TV13)
    - 3-43,44-76. Joel Baumwell, Henry Davis (Box TV13)
    - 3-45-76. New arrival group (Box TV13)
    - 3-46-76. Jim Pollack (Box TV13)
    - 3-47-76. Burger King (Box TV13)
    - 3-48-76. Sherman, Baumwell, Manning (Box TV13)
    - 3-49-76. Retirement party (Florence Cunningham) (Box TV13)
    - 3-50-76. Buck Buchanan (Burger) (Box TV13)
    - 3-50A-76. Burger King hamburger still (Box TV13)
    - 3-51-76. R. Sherman, B. Mannings, Burger King (Box TV13)
    - 3-52,53-76. European-American story (Box TV13)
    - 4-7-76. Marine--Buglers (Box TV13)
    - 4-8-76. Henry David studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 4-10-76. Lighthouse (Box TV13)
    - 4-11-76. New arrival group (Box TV13)
    - 4-12-76. New arrival (Box TV13)
    - 4-13-76. Jesse Kohrman informal (Box TV13)
    - 4-14-76. Jeanne Maraz studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 4-16,17-76. 2 new arrival groups (Box TV13)
    - 4-18-76. Rena Bartos interview (Box TV13)
    - 4-21-76. R. Sherman--J. Rice (Box TV13)
    - 4-23-76. R. Bartos--J. Treasure taping (Box TV13)
    - 4-24-76. Bob Wright studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 4-25-76. Allan Toreano studio portrait (Box TV13)
    - 4-27-76. Creative Head of London office: Bill Seibert, Ron Sherman, Peter Bostock (Box TV13)
    - 1-2-77. Deltacos Seminar (plaza) (No negatives available) (Box TV13)
    - 1-3-77. Typewriter marking (police) (Box TV14)
    - 1-4-77. New arrival group (Box TV14)
    - 1-6-77. Fur group (Box TV14)
    - 1-7-77. Jane Colcins Snowday (Box TV14)
    - 1-8-77. Dominic Telecine (Box TV14)
    - 1-9-77. Hark Cohn and Gail Carlyle (Box TV14)
    - 1-10-77. Atlanta Creative Dir. story: Fred Jolly and group I (Box TV14)
    - 1-11,12-77. Natasha Toby, Caroline Dihel (Box TV14)
    - 1-17-77. International visit war room (Box TV14)
    - 1-18-77. International clients cocktail party (Box TV14)
    - 1-19-77. International exhibition (Box TV14)
    - 1-35-77. International. cocktail party, host Ron Sherman (Box TV14)
    - 1-36-77. Deltacos seminar (U.N.plaza) (Box TV14)
    - 1-37-77. Fred Jolly and group II (Box TV14)
    - 1-38-77. Richard Pollet (Box TV14)
    - 1-40,41,42-77. 3 different New arrival groups (Box TV14)
    - 1-43-77. Art and Craft story I (Box TV14)
    - 1-44-77. Burger King 11th floor construction story (Box TV14)
    - 1-45,46-77. 2 new arrival groups (Box TV14)
    - 1-47-77. art and craft II (Box TV14)
    - 1-48-77. Cafeteria story (Box TV14)
    - 1-49-77. United Fund drawing (Box TV14)
    - 1-50-77. Madison Ave WNEW--Joe Brouillard (Box TV14)
    - 1-51-77. Hugh Connell--Ted Wilson UNICEF (Box TV14)
    - 1-53-77. Retirement party (Box TV14)
    - 1-55-77. 11th Fl. Christmas trees with presents (Box TV14)
    - 1-57-77. New arrival group (Box TV14)
    - 1-58-77. Bill Petty studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-59-77. Mike Tremper studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-62-77. Ernie Emerling studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-63-77. Carolyn Diehl studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-64-77. Merril Snyder studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-65-77. Tom Yamada studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-66-77. Andy Romano studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-67-77. Meeting Room A (R. Sherman) (Box TV14)
    - 1-68-77. Joel Baumwohl studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-70-77. Bill Hennessy studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-71,72-77. 2 new arrival groups (Box TV14)
    - 1-82-77. Tony Herreia (Manila) Art Dir (Box TV14)
    - 1-83-77. Byron Hackett studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-84-77. Interv S. Africa--Ad Age, Rob Irving (Box TV14)
    - 1-85,86-77. John Nasen informal book still (Box TV14)
    - 1-89-77. Group shot (commercial judges) (Box TV14)
    - 1-91-77. Jennifer Walker studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-92-77. Art exhibition (D. Guffy) (Box TV14)
    - 1-93,94-77. 2 new arrival groups (Box TV14)
    - 1-95-77. Yamada Reynolds people (Box TV14)
    - 1-96-77. Research Dept. cleaning (Box TV14)
    - 1-97-77. Don Johnston-Dennis Lanagan (wine) (Box TV14)
    - 1-99-77. Dena Bartos informal (Box TV14)
    - 1-100-77. Bill Tyler (Box TV14)
    - 1-101-77. Rena Bartos studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-103-77. Reynols cover (Box TV14)
    - 1-104-77. John Spillner studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-105-77. Wendekk Pope studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 1-106-77. Jean Maraz informal (Box TV14)
    - 2-1-77. Ruth Downing Karp informal (Box TV14)
    - 2-2-77. Lever 75th anniversary (Box TV14)
    - 2-4-77. Art Directors Club judging (B. Owette) (Box TV14)
    - 2-5-77. Bill Lane (Gold Record) (Box TV14)
    - 2-6-77. Scholarship award: T. Wilson--S. Yuspeh (Box TV14)
    - 2-7,8,9,10,11,12,13-77. Bill Bredekamp, Ed McCallin, Chuck Connor, Ralph Daiuto, John Cox, Ed Lanzo, Don Ferrara (Box TV14)
    - 2-14-77. Japanese guests (Box TV14)
    - 2-15-77. New arrival group (Box TV14)
    - 2-16-77. New arrival group (Box TV14)
    - 2-18-77. Art show (Diony Guffy) (Box TV14)
    - 2-19-77. Amelia Greenstad and Herb Camp award (Box TV14)
    - 2-20-77. Bill Beadle (Box TV14)
    - 2-21,22,23,24-77. Corporate Communication: Dick Eyman, Frank Manaro, Irene Hensen, Wolf Lieschke (Box TV14)
    - 2-25-77. Susan Porter studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 2-31-77. Dennis Altman studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 2-32-77. Ed Hiestand studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 2-33-77. Marty Yazmir studio portrait (Box TV14)
    - 2-38-77. T.U. Taping, D. Johnston, T. Wilson, A. Johns, Dr. Treasurer (Box TV14)
    - 2-40-77. Art directors club award (plaza) (Box TV14)
    - 2-41-77. Giraldi--B. Manning (Box TV14)
    - 2-42-77. Madison Ave T.V. taping-Charlotte Beers (Box TV14)
    - 2-43-77. Corporate Communications group (Box TV14)
    - 2-44-77. Art exhibiton I (Box TV14)
    - 2-47-77. New arrival group (Box TV14)
    - 2-49-77. Art exhibition II (Box TV15)
    - 2-50-77. Wendell Pope informal (Box TV15)
    - 2-51-77. Marty Yazmir informal (Box TV15)
    - 2-53-77. Bike-a-thon (Central Park) (Box TV15)
    - 2-56,57-77. 2 new arrival groups (Box TV15)
    - 2-59-77. Jerry Broderick studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 2-60-77. party Gerry Broderick (Box TV15)
    - 2-61-77. Advertising-Woman (R. Bartos) (Box TV15)
    - 2-62-77. Rheel of the Week Room A Meeting (Bob Heck) (Box TV15)
    - 2-63,64,65-77. George Rosenkranc, Dave Murphy, Sylvia Politis (Box TV15)
    - 2-66-77. Gerry Broderick informal (Box TV15)
    - 2-67-77. Mario Azocar (Chile) interview (Box TV15)
    - 3-1-77. Copy class (David Ostrom, Bernie Owette) (Box TV15)
    - 3-3-77. Effie Awards (Box TV15)
    - 3-4-77. One Show (Alice Tully Hall) (Box TV15)
    - 3-5-77. Salada Tea (New ACC) (Box TV15)
    - 3-6-77. Warren Aldoretta informal (Box TV15)
    - 3-7-77. Sal Shillinglow informal (Box TV15)
    - 3-8-77. Bob Zimmern studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 3-9-77. One Show Award still life (Box TV15)
    - 3-10-77. Photograph exhibition (Box TV15)
    - 3-11-77. Tom Cochran informal (Box TV15)
    - 3-12-77. Granger Tripp studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 3-14-77. CLIO (Box TV15)
    - 3-15-77. B.J. McCabe (Box TV15)
    - 3-16-77. Board of Director guests--Surv. Anglia (Box TV15)
    - 3-17,18-77. Don Johnston, Ted Wilson, Mrs. Barbara Hauptfuhrer (Box TV15)
    - 3-19-77. Joel Baumwell studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 3-20-77. Richard Di'Lallo studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 3-21-77. Arnold Ostrower studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 3-22-77. James Maltese studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 3-23,24-77. 2 new arrival groups (Box TV15)
    - 3-25-77. Joyce Laterne studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 3-26-77. John Davis studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 3-27-77. CLIO group (Kodak) (Box TV15)
    - 3-28-77. Taylor--CBS 21 Club (Box TV15)
    - 3-29,30,31-77. James Maltese informal, Richard Di Lallo informal, Arnold Ostrower informal (Box TV15)
    - 3-32-77. Art exhibition--David Pascall (Box TV15)
    - 3-33-77. Blood group--Don Johnston (Box TV15)
    - 3-35-77. Greg Bathon informal (Box TV15)
    - 3-36-77. R. Sherman--interns group (Box TV15)
    - 3-37-77. John Davis informal (Box TV15)
    - 3-38,39-77. Blood drive truck, Blood drive group (Box TV15)
    - 3-41-77. J.W.T. museum (B. King, H. Connell) (Box TV15)
    - 3-42-77. AMRB moving to 3rd Fl (Box TV15)
    - 3-43-77. Tom Hall informal (Box TV15)
    - 3-44-77. Sandy Maxwell studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 3-46-77. Susanne Procter informal (Box TV15)
    - 3-45to 52-77. Margaret Santo, Ida Burns, Lynn McMillan, Kathleen Krifet, Felecia Gadebod; Floaters: Mary Ducos, Alice Pelzer, Ellen Stwent (Box TV15)
    - 3-53-77. Richard De Pew studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 3-54-77. Lonely Desk (Cover for NY) (Box TV15)
    - 3-56-77. Baseball game I (Box TV15)
    - 3-57-77. Patrick Sherwood informal (Box TV15)
    - 3-59-77. Baseball game II (Box TV15)
    - 3-58-77. Allan Tessier (Box TV15)
    - 3-60-77. Henry Davis informal (Box TV15)
    - 3-61-77. New arrival group (Box TV15)
    - 3-62,63,64,65,66-77. Dick Depew, Sandy Maxwell, Edith Gilson, Bob Frank, Bella Manalo (Box TV15)
    - 3-67,68,69,70,71-77. Research story: Elfrida Von Nardoff, Louis Shapiro, Sonya Yuspeh, Nariman Dhala, Bella Manalo II, John Russel (Box TV15)
    - 3-72-77. Mike Shapiro informal (Box TV15)
    - 3-73-77. European Managers party C (Box TV15)
    - 4-1-77. Forum group (Box TV15)
    - 4-1-77. Joel Baumbwoll informal (Box TV15)
    - 4-3,4,5,6,7-77. Trainee program (Box TV15)
    - 4-8-77. Louis Shapiro (Box TV15)
    - 4-15-77. New arrival group (Box TV15)
    - 4-16-77. French guests (Box TV15)
    - 4-18-77. Tom Hanft studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 4-19-77. Hearb Champ studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 4-20,21-77. Contract signing (D. Johnston, Greg Bathon) (Malcolm Glenn) (Box TV15)
    - 4-27-77. Ed Saunders studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 4-28-77. Mike Millsap (Box TV15)
    - 4-29-77. Robert La Chance studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 4-30-77. Ed Hatcher studio portrait (Box TV15)
    - 4-31,32,33-77. World Processing: Agnes Dengel, Katy Bradley (Box TV15)
    - 1-2 to 9-78. College recruitment program brochure (Ann Wright) (Box TV15)
    - 1-10-78. George Jacoma (Box TV15)
    - 1-11-78. Harry Clark's secretary from London (Box TV15)
    - 1-12-78. Steven Vengrobe (Box TV15)
    - 1-13,14-78. Deltcos--Jack Stevens with guests (Box TV15)
    - 1-15-78. Research meeting (Hotel St. Moritz) (Box TV15)
    - 1-19-78. Joice La Terre (Box TV15)
    - 1-20-78. Art show (Ruler Plain) (Box TV15)
    - 1-21-78. Allan Webb (Box TV15)
    - 1-22,23,24-78. Allen Webb, George Jacoma (Box TV15)
    - 1-25-78. Deltacos group (Box TV15)
    - 1-26-78. Christmas arts and crafts (Box TV16)
    - 1-27-78. Ann Wright and Dick Jones retirement party (Box TV16)
    - 1-28-78. Wolfgang Lieschke (Box TV16)
    - 1-29-78. Dorothy Philips (Box TV16)
    - 1-30-78. Gary Hall (Reel of the Week) (Box TV16)
    - 1-31-78. Wes Hostetter (Box TV16)
    - 1-32-78. Deltacos party (Box TV16)
    - 1-33-78. Ed Saunders (Box TV16)
    - 1-34-78. United Fund drawing (Joel Baumwoll) (Box TV16)
    - 1-35-78. Kraft press conference (Box TV16)
    - 1-36-78. Ed Hatcher (Box TV16)
    - 1-37-78. Carolyn Demy (Box TV16)
    - 1-38-78. Connie Ivie group (Box TV16)
    - 1-39-78. Sadie farewell (Box TV16)
    - 1-40-78. Jess Korman farewell (Box TV16)
    - 1-41-78. Steve Vengrove (Box TV16)
    - 1-42-78. Tom Hanft (Box TV16)
    - 1-43-78. Bob La Chance (Box TV16)
    - 1-44,45-78. Christmas presents 11th floor, JWT Christmas wreath (Box TV16)
    - 1-46-78. Elevator, Harold (Box TV16)
    - 1-48-78. UNICEF--H. Connel, children (Box TV16)
    - 1-49-78. Bob Boregard (Box TV16)
    - 1-51-78. Wesley Hostetter (Box TV16)
    - 1-52-78. Dorothy Philips (Box TV16)
    - 1-54-78. Art exhibition I--11th floor (Box TV16)
    - 1-55-78. Art exhibition II--9th floor (Box TV16)
    - 1-56-78. Harold Connelly (Box TV16)
    - 1-57-78. Reel of the Week (Box TV16)
    - 1-58-78. Association National Advertising T.V. workshop--Marion Preston, Dick Bennett (Box TV16)
    - 1-59-78. Harry Clark (Box TV16)
    - 1-60-78. Natasha Toby V.P (Box TV16)
    - 1-62-78. Trainee presentation (Box TV16)
    - 1-64-78. Peter Grounds V.P (Box TV16)
    - 1-65-78. Art exhibition (Box TV16)
    - 1-67-78. John Kahmer V.P (Box TV16)
    - 2-1-78. Award group--Lou Philip, John Nasen, Takama (Box TV16)
    - 2-2-78. Natasha Toby II V.P (Box TV16)
    - 2-3-78. New arrival group (Box TV16)
    - 2-7,8,9-78. Baseball--Mets logo; Ray Tarber; Louise Murray (Box TV16)
    - 2-11-78. Howard Willens (Box TV16)
    - 2-12,13,14,15,16,17-78. Kent Hansen, Ed Veleker, George Jacoma, Rena Bartos, Ginny Bahr, Ed Gerard (Box TV16)
    - 2-18-78. Jerry Scorse and children (Box TV16)
    - 2-19-78. Library Paperback exchange (Box TV16)
    - 2-46,47-78. Allan Tessier (Box TV16)
    - 2-49-78. International Managers--Room A (Box TV16)
    - 2-51-78. Annual Meeting (Box TV16)
    - 2-52,53-78. International Lunch, setting of rooms kitchen group (Box TV16)
    - 2-54-78. Florence Karnes (Box TV16)
    - 2-55-78. Smoking story (Box TV16)
    - 2-56-78. Wayne Fickinger party (Box TV16)
    - 2-57-78. National Secretaries Week (Box TV16)
    - 2-58-78. Fortune award--Bill He-----, Bob Huff (Box TV16)
    - 2-60,61-78. Scrabble group I,II (Box TV16)
    - 2-62-78. Sylvia Polytis (Box TV16)
    - 2-64-78. Advertising Women--Rena Bartos, B. Seibert; Hotel Pierre (Box TV16)
    - 2-65-78. Frank Breiter (Box TV16)
    - 2-66-78. Moving (Box TV16)
    - 2-67-78. Contract signing--Don Johnston (Box TV16)
    - 2-68-78. Bill Tyler (speaker) (Box TV16)
    - 2-74-78. Rena Bartos (Box TV16)
    - 3-2-78. Art Directors exhibition (Box TV16)
    - 3-3-78. Effie Awards (Box TV16)
    - 3-4-78. Howard Abrahams (Box TV16)
    - 3-7-78. Joanne Folin (Box TV16)
    - 3-10,11-78. Andre van Stom (Box TV16)
    - 3-12-78. CLIO (Box TV16)
    - 3-14,15-78. Arthur Cohen (Box TV16)
    - 3-20,21-78. 2 new arrival groups (Box TV16)
    - 3-22-78. Baseball--Mets office (Box TV16)
    - 3-23-78. Entertainment group--Sy Kolman recording (Box TV16)
    - 3-25-78. Cohen Arthur (Box TV16)
    - 3-26-78. Black Eye story--Tom Sheridan (Box TV16)
    - 3-28-78. Contract signing (Don Johnston) (Box TV16)
    - 3-29-78. Art Directors Award (Box TV16)
    - 3-30-78. Reggie Client (J. Athes) (Box TV16)
    - 3-3-78. Gabe Samwels (Box TV16)
    - 3-32-78. Klorman Harvey (Box TV16)
    - 3-33-78. Burger King group (Box TV16)
    - 3-36-78. New arrival group (Box TV16)
    - 3-38-78. New arrival group (Box TV16)
    - 3-39-78. John Stuart (Box TV16)
    - 3-40-78. Lee Pratt (Box TV16)
    - 3-41-78. John Overaker (Box TV16)
    - 3-43-78. I Love NY (Box TV16)
    - 3-44,45,46,47,48-78. Vernon Wright, Tom Goodman, Steve Dembner, Carol Nelson, Norm Perkins (Box TV16)
    - 3-49-78. Stan Tarner (Box TV16)
    - 3-50-78. Melissa Mohr studio portrait (Box TV16)
    - 3-51-78. Regina Kelly studio portrait (Box TV16)
    - 3-52-78. Marion Preston party (Box TV16)
    - 3-53-78. 20th Century Fox poster (Box TV16)
    - 3-58-78. CEBA cocktail party (Box TV16)
    - 3-56 to 63-78. Dick Pell, Joice La Terre, Daly Derry, Regis Albrecht, Michelle Hale, Marie Watts, Frank Verlizzo, Elenor Newman (Box TV16)
    - 3-64-78. Trainees for ad brochure (Cynthia Perry) (Box TV16)
    - 3-65-78. Michael Nwaobi (Box TV16)
    - 3-67-78. Meeting Mouse (Box TV16)
    - 3-70,71-78. Paul Waxman, Jerry Aiello (Box TV17)
    - 3-72,73-78. Leni Salz (Box TV17)
    - 3-74-78. Telecine--Construction (Box TV17)
    - 3-75-78. New arrivals 2 group (Box TV17)
    - 4-1-78. Marion Holder (Box TV17)
    - 4-2-78. New arrival group (Box TV17)
    - 4-3-78. Bob Donnellan (Box TV17)
    - 4-21-78. New arrival group (Box TV17)
    - 4-22,23,24-78. George DeMaria, Mary Weber, David Tonkonow (Box TV17)
    - 4-30-78. The Boys from Brazil group (Box TV17)
    - 4-31-78. Boys from Brazil Wes Shaw alone (Box TV17)
    - 4-34-78. CEBA Awards (Box TV17)
    - 4-35,36-78. Gorey display (Box TV17)
    - 1-38,39-78. Trainee brochure Cynthia Perry (Box TV17)
    - 4-40-78. SMTPE (Box TV17)
    - 4-49-78. Connie Ivie (Box TV17)
    - 4-54-78. Ford pick-up t-shirt girls (Box TV17)
    - 4-56-78. United Fund group (Box TV17)
    - 4-57-78. United Fund meeting (Box TV17)
    - 4-59-78. Christmas chorus (Box TV17)
    - 4-60,61,62,63,64,65-78. Carlton Humphrey, Nancy Erickson, Oerr Horigan, Lois Shapiro, Ann Koesher, Fred DeBoer (Box TV17)
    - 4-66-78. A. Gillis, Patti Laura N.Y. Thompson group (Box TV17)
    - 4-67-78. Basketball team game (Box TV17)
    - 4-68,69,70,71-78. Sam Laddy, J. Baumwell, Tom Mabley, Art Kramer, Bill Lane (Box TV17)
    - 1-1-79. Lori Birnbaum (Box TV17)
    - 1-3-79. Macy's shopping bag (Box TV17)
    - 1-4-79. United Fund drawing (Box TV17)
    - 1-7-79. Robin Restall (Box TV17)
    - 1-8,9-79. 2 new arrival groups (Box TV17)
    - 1-10-79. Norm Varney (Box TV17)
    - 1-11-79. Bert Peller (Wall St. Journal) (Box TV17)
    - 1-12,13,14-79. Trainee meetings (Nationwide): B.Howison, J. Cox, J. Brouillard, J. Traice (Box TV17)
    - 1-15-79. 5 different Picasso art (Box TV17)
    - 1-16-79. Entertainment party: Don Johnston, Ron Sherman (Box TV17)
    - 1-18-79. Deltacos poster (moving) (Box TV17)
    - 1-19-79. Lever group party (Box TV17)
    - 1-20-79. Mimi Emilita (Box TV17)
    - 1-21-79. Greg Bathon Annual Report (Box TV17)
    - 1-24-79. Allun Johns Annual Report (Box TV17)
    - 1-25,26-79. Chick Blood, Esther Mulder (Box TV17)
    - 1-27,28-79. Poster, Sheron Gordon (Box TV17)
    - 1-30-79. Wayne Flickinger Annual Report (Box TV17)